Jane Ellis Papers, Inclusive: 1949-1998, undated, Bulk: 1974-1995
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Subject Files, 1971-1997, undated; 3
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Church: Relations with Other Denominations, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subject File: True Orthodox (Catacomb) Church (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Subject File: True Orthodox (Catacomb) Church (2 of 2), 1970, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Subject File: Bogorodichnyi Tsentr. General, 1990-1993, 2019 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Subject File: Bogorodichnyi Tsentr: Publications: Bogorodichnyi sobor, no. 1, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Subject File: Bogorodichnyi Tsentr: Publications: Bogorodichnyi sobor, no. 2, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Subject File: Bogorodichnyi Tsentr: Publications: Bogorodichnyi sobor, no. 4, 1992 July (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Subject File: Bogorodichnyi Tsentr: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Lists, 1979-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Index, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Retired before 1991, 1982-1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Deceased before 1991, 1971-1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Alexi (Ridiger), 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Afanasi (Kudyuk)-Avgustin, 1988-1990, 1993, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Deviatov (Rostislav)-Dmitri (Kapalin), 1990, 1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthdox Bishops: Feodor (Gaiun)-Filaret (Vakhromeev), 1987-1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Gavriil (Stebliuchenko)-Grigory (Chirkov), 1983, 1988-1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Hippolyte (Hilko)-Khrizostom (Martishk), 1988, 1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Iakov (Panchuk)-Isidor (Kirichenko), 1989, 1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Kliment (Kapalin)-Kronid (Mishenko), 1990-1993, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Kirill (Gundyaev), 1985, 1988-1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Lazar (Shvets)-Leonid (Talypin), 1989-1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Makari (Svistun)-Mikhail (Raskovalov), 1980-1988, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Nifont (Solodukha)-Nikon (Vasukov), 1989-1993, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Onufrii (Berezovskii), 1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Paisii (Samchuk)-Pyotr (Karpusuk), 1990-1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Sanchuk-Stefan (Korzun), 1989, 1992, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Tikhon (Emelyanov), undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Vadim (Lazebny)-Vsevolod (Vasil'tsev), 1977, 1989-1992, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Yelevfery (Kosaryev)-Yuvenali (Tarasov), 1988-1989, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Subject File: Russian Orthodox Bishops: Abroad, 1966, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: General (1 of 6), 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: General (2 of 6), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: General (3 of 6), 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: General (4 of 6), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: General (5 of 6), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: General (6 of 6), 1995-1997, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Correspondence: Funding: General, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Correspondence: Funding: Ernst Van Eeghen, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Correspondence: Funding: OMSC, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Working Group, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Research Proposal, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: List of Orthodox Bishops, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Legislature on Religion, 1993, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Hostility toward Evangelicals, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Russian Protestants, 1992-1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Non-Evangelical Protestants, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Views of the Moscow Patriarchate, 1992-1997, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Elliott, Mark, 1993-1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Fairbairn, Don (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Fairbairn, Don (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Robeck, Cecil M., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Contacts, 1994-1998, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Anonymous Thesis Manuscript: Chapter IV and Chapter V, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Subject File: Orthodox-Protestant Dialog: Soviet Special Focus Report (1978): Correspondence, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Subject File: Russia and Russian Orthodox Church: Clippings, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Personal, 1991, 1998; 4
  The smallest series, Personal, contains Jane Ellis’ graduate school application and copies of her obituaries.
  - Application for Graduate Study at Oxford University, 1991 April (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Obituaries, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)